#### **About Me**

I'm a developer with over 2.5 years of coding experience in backend development. During this time, I've worked on projects and gained a understanding of programming. I'm constantly seeking new challenges and opportunities to expand my skills and knowledge.

### Objective

I'm deeply passionate about working in the fields of AI and cybersecurity. I am eager to contribute my skills to a dynamic team that values innovation and problem-solving. I am excited to explore new opportunities in this exciting and evolving industry.

#### **Personal Details**

Date of Birth 14-12-2001

Nationality Pakistani

Marital Status Single

on igic

Mail areeshawaseem1416@gm ail.com

Contact No 03322438858

#### **Social Links**

linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/i n/areesha-waseem-0a78bb238

Fiverr

https://www.fiverr.com/ar eesha1412? public\_mode=true

#### Skills

AI - Experienced
Programming skill - Expert
Database - Beginner
ASP.NET MVC - Experienced
Teamwork - Experienced

# AREESHA WASEEM

Developer

## Experience

#### Al Engineer July 2023-Present

As an AI Engineer at Swag-Kicks, I am actively involved in the development and implementation of machine learning algorithms and models. My contributions to AI-driven projects have not only enhanced product features but have also improved user experiences. I collaborate closely with cross-functional teams to drive innovation and achieve our goals.

#### Digital Marketing June 2022-Jan 2023

I've worked on diverse NFT projects, using social media and community engagement to generate excitement and wider recognition.

#### **Teaching**

August 2019 - January 2021

During my time at The Nation Public School, I had the opportunity to teach Computer Science to secondary level students in both lab and theory

#### Education

Bachelor in Computer Science PAF KIET North Campus Karachi 2021-present

Intermediate in Pre-Engineering For Women Nazimabad Karachi 2018-2020

Matriculation in Science S.M Public Academy Karachi 2017-2018

#### **Acheivements**

Pakistan Day 2022

Runner-up for Speed Programming Competition in KIET Technology Pakistan Day.

## Language

- Urdu Native
- English Good